In your life, you want to fulfill all your dreams -
a home for your family,
a secure future for your children, a place to
celebrate an achievement, a
holiday abroad and much more. So, to make
each of our dreams come true, it
is important to have a plan that provides financial security
to the family in case of any unfortunate eventuality and
also helps you build a savings corpus. Introducing
ICICI Prove Future Perfect,
an ideal plan for savings and protection that
provides financial security for you and your family along with a lump sum savings on maturity.
This plan offers savings with the feature of guarantee.
You will get a guaranteed maturity
benefit which is a
guaranteed lump sum paid on maturity of the policy. Guaranteed
Additions are received as a percentage of the annual premium. Not
only this,
it also offers the possibility of increasing your wealth through bonuses.
You
can increase your maturity amount through Reverse Bonuses which can be declared during the policy term and
get a terminal bonus, if any, at the end of the policy term. This plan
also has the flexibility to choose the premium payment term, premium payment mode and policy term as per your requirement.
ICICI Prudential Future Perfect also provides you and
your family with life cover throughout the policy term.
Furthermore,
the plan offers tax benefits on premiums paid and benefits earned.
Let's now see how this plan
works. Suppose you are a 35-year-old
male and have
decided to invest in ICICI Prudential Future Perfect.
You choose a premium payment term of 10 years, a
policy term of 20 years, and
pay an annual premium of ₹0,000.
At the end of the policy term, you are
expected to receive a maturity benefit of ₹74,000 at a 8 PRA RR,
which
includes a guaranteed maturity benefit of ₹22,950, an
accumulated addition of ₹82,500, a
vested retirement bonus of ₹
12,835, and a
terminal
bonus of ₹64,271. The maturity benefit at a 4 PRA RR will be ₹
47,000.
In case of an unfortunate event, the nominee gets life cover. So,
what are you waiting for? Join
ICICI to fulfill your dreams.
Invest in a Proof Future Perfect Plan today
[Music]